Finding Aid for the Ray Bolger Papers LSC.1117
UCLA Library Special Collections
Ray Bolger papers
1923-1987
1940s-1980s
UCLA Library Special Collections
Bolger, Ray
LSC.1117
60.0 Linear Feet (85 boxes, 2 record cartons, 39 flat boxes, 2 shoe boxes, and 10 sound recording boxes)
Among his many roles on stage, screen and television in a career that spanned sixty years, American comedian and dancer Ray Bolger was best known for his role as the Scarecrow in the 1939 film, The Wizard of Oz. In addition to his work in film and television, he continually returned to the stage, often appearing in one-man shows. The collection consists of script material, contracts, clippings, correspondence, photographs, music, and ephemera related to Bolger's lengthy career.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9969539333606533
Biography
Raymond Wallace Bolger was born on January 10, 1904, in Dorchester, Massachusetts. As a teenager, he danced on street corners in Boston and began his acting career performing in amateur theatricals. He made his stage debut with the Bob Ott Musical Comedy Repertory Company in 1922 and was soon appearing in vaudeville with Gus Edwards. Not long after, he appeared in Broadway productions of By Jupiter, George White's Scandals, Keep Off the Grass, Life Begins at 8:40, and On Your Toes, in which he won praise for his dancing skills in a number choreographed by George Balanchine. In time, he began appearing in musical films such as The Great Ziegfeld, Rosalie, Sunny, Sweethearts, and his most well-known film, The Wizard of Oz. During World War II, he helped organize U.S.O. shows that toured American military and naval bases around the world.
In 1948, he returned to Broadway and starred in a three-year run of Where's Charley, which catapulted his stage career and lead to a film version of the story, starring Bolger, in 1952. That same year Bolger made his television debut with The Colgate Comedy Hour, and from 1953-1955 he starred in his own television show The Ray Bolger Show on ABC. Originally titled Where's Raymond in the first season, the show cast Bolger as Raymond Wallace, a Broadway star living in suburbia. Bolger and his wife Gwen were the owners of their own production company, B&R Enterprises, which produced Where's Raymond/The Ray Bolger Show. In 1957, he starred in Washington Square and made numerous guest appearances on television shows, such as Hollywood Palace, The Jimmy Durante Show, The Judy Garland Show, and The Red Skelton Hour. During this time, he continued to work in motion pictures, appearing in films such as April in Paris, Babes in Toyland, and The Runner Stumbles. In between his work in film and television, Bolger continued to perform on the stage, appearing in one-man shows and song-and-dance concerts as well as stage musicals such as All American, Come Summer, and The Happy Time.
Bolger was involved with a number of philanthropic causes, including the American Red Cross and the American Heart Association, and in political advocacy, appearing and performing at numerous events. He was also an avid golfer, often competing in celebrity tournaments; and he was also involved in various business ventures, including real estate. Ray Bolger died of cancer on January 15, 1987 in Los Angeles, California.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material related to the career of comedian, dancer, and actor Ray Bolger. Included in the collection is script material, contractual documents, correspondence, clippings, photographs, music, and ephemera related to Bolger's career. Notably absent are original materials relating to the production of the 1939 film Wizard of Oz.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Biographical and Personal
Television Projects
Motion Picture Projects
Stage Projects
Radio Projects
Audio Recording and Short Film Projects
Sound Recordings
Armed Services Entertainment
Appearances and Events
Unidentified Projects
Correspondence
Photographs
Clippings
Ephemera
Awards, Honors, and Certificates
Business, Financial, and Legal
Music
Scrapbooks
Writings By or About Bolger
Publications
Actors -- United States -- Archives; Bolger, Ray--Archives.
- Series 1. Biographical and Personal, no date, ca. 1920s-1930s, 1970s-1980s; Boxes 79 and 110
  Scope and Contents note
  The Personal and Biographical series is a small amount of personal documents relating to Bolger. This includes biographical and personal documents, a trunk inventory, and planners/day log books. For more biographical information, see the series Writings By or About Bolger.
  - Biographical and personal documents, no date, ca. 1920s-1930s, 1970s-1980s (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Ceramic mask of Bolger, 1934 (Box 120)
- Series 2. Television Projects., ca. 1950s-1980s.; Boxes 1-9, 11-13, 15, 20, 34-37, 44, 53, 74, 76-79, 103-104, 117, 137
  The Television Projects mainly represents Wheres Raymond and/or The Ray Bolger Show. Included are scripts and legal documents such as TV rerun sheets, contracts, and music clearances. Additionally, there are scripts documenting Bolgers appearances on a variety of popular television programs such as Battlestar Galactica, Diff'rent Strokes, The Entertainer, General Electric Theater, The Hollywood Palace, The Partridge Family and a small amount of publicity, production information, treatments, outlines, correspondence, clippings, and photographs. See the Music Series for orchestral parts that appear to be from The Ray Bolger Show. The series is arranged alphabetically by projects.
  - All in the Family
    General note
    Episode title: Archie Works Out.
    - Script, 1977 (Box 23)
  - Count Your Blessings
    - Count Your Blessings - script, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Count Your Blessings - script, no date (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Dean Martin Show (The)
    - Bolger spot scripts, no date (Box 79, Folder 7)
      Appears to be for The Dean Martin Show.
  - Entertainer (The)
    - Casting call poster, no date (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Contract, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Contract paperwork, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and publicity, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Photocopied clippings, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, 1976 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Script, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      With some production material.
  - Fantasy Island
    - Fantasy Island - script, no date (Box 27, Folder 6)
      Episode titled: A Very Strange Affair/ The Sailor.
  - General Electric Theater (The)
    - Girl with the Flaxen Hair (The), 1958 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Girl with the Flaxen Hair (The) slides, no date (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Profile (The) script, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Guest Appearance
    - 51st Annual Academy Awards - presentation segment, photographs, and clippings, no date, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Aloha Paradise - script, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      For episode #5.
    - Baretta - script, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Episode title: Just for Laughs.
    - Battlestar Galactica - script, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Episode title: Greetings from Earth.
    - Buick-Berle Show (The) - script, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Captains and the Kings - script, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Colgate Comedy Hour (The) - script and publicity, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Diff'rent Strokes final draft script, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Diff'rent Strokes table draft scripts, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Donny and Marie Show (The) - still, no date, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Ginger Rogers Show (The) script, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Removed from cover labeled Lets Go It's Bolger for preservation purposes.
    - Hollywood Palace - contract, 1965-1966, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Hollywood Palace - first draft script, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      For show #6. Removed from cover labeled The Hollywood Palace for preservation purposes.
    - Hollywood Palace - script, 1965, no date (Box 15, Folder 8)
      For show #7. Removed from cover labeled The Hollywood Palace for preservation purposes.
    - Hollywood Palace - second and final draft scripts, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      For show #7.
    - Jimmy Durante Show - script material, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Little House on the Prairie - script, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Episode title: Dance with Me.
    - Merv Griffin Show (The) - Newsweek stills, 1976 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Partridge Family (The) - record disc, no date (Box 138)
    - Partridge Family (The) scripts, 1970, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Episode titles: What Ever Happened to the Old Songs? and The Modfather.
    - Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall - script, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Removed from cover labeled Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall; Ray Bolger 1962.
    - Red Skelton Hour (The) - Mayor of Central Park sketch, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Removed from red cover labeled Ray Bolger for preservation purposes, see Box 117.
    - Revlon Revue Accent on Comedy - script, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Script covers, no date (Box 117)
      For The Hollywood Palace, Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall, The Ginger Rogers Show, and The Red Skelton Hour.
  - It's Always Christmas
    - Harry Haldane sketches for Its Always Christmas television series, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lanigan's Rabbi
    - The Cadaver in the Clutter script, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Life and Times of Grizzly Adams
    - Life and Times of Grizzly Adams (The) - script, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Episode title: Marvin the Magnificent.
  - Peter and the Magic Egg
    - Clippings, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Press party press clippings and photographs, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Wonderment of Peter Paas (The) script, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Final title: Peter and the Magic Egg.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The)
    - ABC Display Board, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Angel in Disguise, no date (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Barber Takes a Bride (The), no date (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Cast lists, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Contracts, 1953-1954 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Double Life (A), no date (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Efficiency Expert (The), no date (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Episode synopses - The Ray Bolger Show, 1961 Aug 29 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      See also: Ray Bolger Show (The) (Where's Raymond) episode synopses for Where's Raymond.
    - Father for a Day, no date (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Duplicate script,
    - Father for a Day, no date (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Getting Susan a Job, no date (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Gift from the Sultan (A), no date (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Girl on the Billboard, no date (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Guild agreements, ca. 1950-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Herman, the Wonder Dog, no date (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Ideal Husband, no date (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Ideal Husband, no date (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Jealousy, no date (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Katie Gets Glamorized, no date (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Last of the Showboats, no date (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Legal documents, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Legal documents, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Legal documents, 1960, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Some appear to be from B & R Enterprises and the Music Publishers Holding Corporation.
    - Legal documents, 1953-1956, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Some appear to be from B & R Enterprises and the William Morris Agency.
    - Legal documents, 1953-1954, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Legal documents, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Legal documents, 1953-1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Legal documents, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Legal documents, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Letter of non-renewal with profits and loss return, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Letter regarding The Ray Bolger Show film reels, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Man of the Year, no date (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Masquerade is Over (The), 1954 Jul 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Miss Teen Ager, no date (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Music clearances, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Navy Show (The), no date (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Navy Show (The), no date (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Night School, no date (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Notes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Novelist (The), no date (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Photocopied music schedules, 1954-1955 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Pitch pages, no date (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Appear to be pitch pages.
    - Predatory Female, no date (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Professor Sniff, no date (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Professor Sniff, no date (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Duplicate script.
    - Publicity Pete, no date (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Ray Bolger Show sponsors spots, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      For episodes 6A and 8.
    - Ray Helps Young Married Couple, no date (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Ray Humanizes Pete, no date (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Ray's Ex Partner, no date (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Ray's Mother and Father, 1955 Feb 18 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Reruns contracts, 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Reunion of Squad B, no date (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Script, no date (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Script, no date (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Script, 1954 Aug 19 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Script material, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Ray Bolger Television Pilot Film by Ken Englund; Here's Bolger, Ray Bolger Show scripts and Here's Bolger outline by John Murray and Ben Freedman. May be related to Where's Raymond.
    - Script material by Ben Freedman and John Fenton Murray, no date (Box 9, Folder 7)
      With outlines, format, and notes. May be related to Where's Raymond. Script material by Jean Holloway.
    - Script Pages, no date (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Appears to be for Ray Bolger Show.
    - Script pages, no date (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Script pages, no date (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Script pages, no date (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Seeing Double, no date (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Show #15A, no date (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Stag at Bay, no date (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Statements of estimated negative costs, 1954-1955 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      Some appear to be for Where's Raymond. See also: Box 78 Folder 1.
    - Statements of estimated negative costs, 1954-1955 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show. See also: Box 78 Folder 2.
    - Teenagers (The), no date (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Television Pilot Film - script pages, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Script pages by Alan Lipscott and Bob Fisher. Script written by Ken Englund. With Shoe on the Other Foot script pages.
    - Television Pilot Film- script pages, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Script pages by Alan Lipscott and Bob Fisher. Script written by Ken Englund.
    - The Efficiency Expert - script, no date (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Bolger Walks Again: music (Box 19, Box 57)
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) (Where's Raymond)
    - Best Dressed Man, 1954 Mar 24 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Episode synopses - Where's Raymond, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      See also: The Ray Bolger Show episode synopses.
    - Foster Fathers, no date (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Appears to be Ray Bolger Show (Where's Raymond) script.
    - Let's Get Ray Married - show 25 script, 1954 Mar 25 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Photocopied music schedules, 1953-1954 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Press clippings, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Production budget and costs report, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Production material, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Production material, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ray Plays the Stork - show 24 script, 1954 Mar 18 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Redecorate Coffee Pot - show 20 scripts, 1954 Jan 11 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook of clippings, 1953 (Box 53)
    - Script, no date (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Script, 1953 Dec 22 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Script pages, no date (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Script pages, 1953 Oct 29 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Appears to be Where's Raymond.
    - Script pages, 1953 Dec 6 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Script pages, 1953 July 27 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Script pages, 1953 Dec 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Shoe Store (The) - show 26 scripts, 1954 Apr 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Show #10 - script, 1953 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Show #11 - script, 1953 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Show #12 - script, 1953 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Show 1 - script, 1953 Aug 25 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Show 13 - script, 1953 Nov 22 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Show 13 - script pages, 1953 Nov 19 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Show 15 - script pages, no date (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Show 16 - script pages, 1953 Dec 15 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Show 17, no date (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Show 17 - script, 1953 Dec 27 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Show 18 - script, 1953 Dec 30 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Show 18 - script pages, 1954 Jan 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Show 19 - script, 1954 Jan 8 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Show 2 - script, 1953 Sep 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Show 2 - script, 1953 Sep 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Show 20 and 22 - scripts, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Show 23 and 24 - scripts, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Show 27 - script, 1954 Apr 8 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Show 3 - script, 1953 Sep 4 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Show 4 - script, 1953 Sep 12 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Show 5 - script, 1953 Sep 19 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Show 6 - script, 1953 Sep 29 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Show 7 - script, 1953 Oct 7 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Show 8 - script, 1953 Oct 19 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Show 9 - script, 1953 Oct 23 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Syndication booking documents, 1960-1961, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Transcription discs (36 discs), no date (Box 137)
      May be related to The Ray Bolger Show.
    - Where's Raymond - script pages, no date (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Who's Getting Married - show 21 script, 1954 Feb 25 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Senior Citizen Shuffle (The)
    - First draft and revised scripts, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      Appears to be produced.
  - Supertrain
    - Supertrain - script, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      Episode title: Where Have You Been, Billy Boy?
  - Three on a Date
    - Publicity stills, 1978 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Scripts, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square
    - Clippings, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Ephemera, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Letters to Bolger, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Publicity stills and negatives, no date (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Publicity stills and negatives, no date (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Publicity stills and negatives, no date (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Script, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      With publicity and letters.
    - Statements of income and loss, 1957 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Series 3. Motion Picture Projects, ca. 1930s-1980s; Boxes 9-10, 33-36, 38, 74, 76, 80, 103, 115, 131-132
  The series includes a small amount of scripts, publicity, correspondence, film stills, and clippings related to film projects in which Bolger was associated. Films represented include: April in Paris, Babes in Toyland, The Great Ziegfeld, Roaslie, The Runner Stumbles, Sunny, Thats Dancing, Two of a Kind, and Where's Charley?. Notably absent are original materials relating to the production of the 1939 film The Wizard of Oz except for a very small number of clippings, sheet music, and a facsimile copy of a cast and crew contact list. The series is arranged alphabetically by project.
  - April in Paris, no date (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - April In Paris - contract, Mar 1952 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - April in Paris - script, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    With correspondence and clippings.
  - Babes in Toyland - album, no date, 1961 (Box 115)
    4 items.
  - Babes in Toyland - clippings, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Babes in Toyland - contract, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Babes in Toyland - script, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    With Box Office Blue Ribbon award certificate.
  - Great Ziegfeld (The) - telegram, memorandum, and lyrics, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Rosalie - clippings, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Rosalie - still, no date (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Rosalie - stills and ephemera, no date (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Runner Stumbles (The) - clippings, 1978-1980 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Runner Stumbles (The) - publicity and thank you letters, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    With one still. Clippings removed for preservation purposes.
  - Runner Stumbles (The) - script and executed contract, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Runner Stumbles (The) - script and production information, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    With published play in two acts.
  - Runner Stumbles (The) - still, no date (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Sunny - clippings, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Sunny - stills, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Sunny - stills, no date (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - That's Dancing! - clippings, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - That's Dancing! - group portrait, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Two of a Kind - script, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Released as Just You and Me Kid.
  - Where's Charley? - clippings, 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Where's Charley? - ephemera, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Where's Charley? - final script by John Monks, Jr., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Where's Charley? - photographs, no date (Box 103, Folder 15)
    Appears to be for the motion picture production of Where's Charley. See also Stage Projects.
  - Where's Charley? - scripts, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Where's Charley? - scripts, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Where's Charley? - stills, no date (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Wizard of Oz - commercial sheet music, 1939 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Wizard of Oz (The) - clippings, no date, 1943, 1970s-1980s (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Wizard of Oz (The) - clippings, 1939 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Wizard of Oz cast and crew contact list, 1939 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Facsimile.
- Series 4. Stage Projects, ca. 1930s-1980s; Boxes 2, 13-16, 27, 29, 33-38, 41, 43-44, 48, 50, 53, 74, 76-78, 102-104, 107-108,114-115
  The Stage Projects series consists of material documenting Bolgers work in the theater, club appearances, and concerts. Projects represented include productions such as All American, By Jupiter, Come Summer, On Your Toes, Wheres Charley and live appearances at the Empire Room at the Waldorf Astoria and numerous Las Vegas engagements. Included are scripts, contracts, fan mail, clippings, and a small amount of publicity, ephemera, and photographs. The series is arranged alphabetically by project.
  - All American, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - All American - Act II outline, 1961, no date (Box 13, Folder 4)
    With publicity and ephemera.
  - All American - album recording, no date (Box 115)
    3 items.
  - All American - clippings, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - All American - contract, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - All American - correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - All American - ephemera, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - All American - letters to Bolger, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - All American - scrapbook, 1962 (Box 53)
  - All American - scripts, 1961, no date (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - All American - telegrams, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Most addressed to Winter Garden Theater.
  - All American, Wires, etc. and Josh Logan material, ca. 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    From envelop labeled: Nice Letters, All American, Wires, etc. and Josh Logan Material
  - All's Fair - clippings, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    With three programs.
  - Beau Nash - clippings and publicity, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    With photographs.
  - Beau Nash - research, no date, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Broadmoor International Theater - ephemera and correspondence, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    With clippings.
  - By Jupiter - clippings, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - By Jupiter - photographs, no date (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - By Jupiter - photographs, no date (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - By Jupiter - script, no date (Box 13, Folder 7)